{
    "name": "Italian/DaysAndMonths.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "venerdi",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1445274012.8059216,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Friday\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "quattordici",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445273949.7033124,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"14\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "ottobre",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445273970.6125083,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"October\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "marzo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445274008.6186821,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"March\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "domencia",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445273996.0139613,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sunday\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "giugno",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445273975.9158115,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"June\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Giovedi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445273992.8277788,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Thursday\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "settanta",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445273954.538589,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"70\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "6",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445274083.687976,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sei\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "diciannove",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445274089.5863132,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"19\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lenedi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445274023.6715431,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Monday\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "gennaio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445274080.1707747,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"January\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "quindici",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445274017.7462041,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"15\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "dicembre",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445274070.752236,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"December\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "luglio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445274093.4605348,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"July\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "febbraio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445274076.5175657,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"February\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "sedici",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1444930066.6512344,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"16\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "cinquanta",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1444930005.2706256,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"50\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "quaranta",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1444930193.3854587,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"40\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "sessanta",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1444930331.6400037,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"60\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "quattro",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1445274113.1966636,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"4\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "mercoledi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1445274097.2857535,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Wednesday\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "diciotto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1444930001.1653183,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"18\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "cento",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1444930111.3928134,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"100\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "maggio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1444930287.4912255,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"May\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ottanta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930135.2677557,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"80\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "14",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930514.9631286,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quattordici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "agosto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930051.5329075,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"August\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "uno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930181.5930376,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"1\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "4",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930042.209691,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quattro\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "20",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930261.87718,
            "question": "Given the definition \"venti\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "8",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930143.1039696,
            "question": "Given the definition \"otto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sei",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930088.4332728,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"6\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "June",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930267.2279894,
            "question": "Given the definition \"giugno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sette",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930044.6326952,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"7\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "90",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930400.4038258,
            "question": "Given the definition \"novanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "novembre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930504.1835096,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"November\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "December",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930501.5889049,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dicembre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "7",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930151.871185,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sette\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Saturday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930386.0967002,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sabato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "August",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930271.1591964,
            "question": "Given the definition \"agosto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "15",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930145.631174,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quindici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "tre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930237.7788374,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"3\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "due",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930373.1698775,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"2\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "dodici",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930235.298433,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"12\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "17",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930409.8306425,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dicassette\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "3",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930179.7366345,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "February",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930264.9815855,
            "question": "Given the definition \"febbraio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "dicassette",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444929976.2114742,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"17\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "18",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930168.5982149,
            "question": "Given the definition \"diciotto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "April",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930388.3587043,
            "question": "Given the definition \"aprile\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "January",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930317.0676777,
            "question": "Given the definition \"gennaio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "nove",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930406.0142357,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"9\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Tuesday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930322.6231878,
            "question": "Given the definition \"martedi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "March",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930391.8063104,
            "question": "Given the definition \"marzo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "martedi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930296.4350412,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Tuesday\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Friday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930403.939432,
            "question": "Given the definition \"venerdi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "undici",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930149.7807813,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"11\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "novanta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930423.0332658,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"90\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "60",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930363.1639595,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sessanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "May",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444929970.1692634,
            "question": "Given the definition \"maggio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "80",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444929992.018702,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ottanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Wednesday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930285.0214212,
            "question": "Given the definition \"mercoledi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "10",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930365.176363,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dieci\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "cinque",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930371.5243745,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"5\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "July",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930443.348302,
            "question": "Given the definition \"luglio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sabato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930085.9372685,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Saturday\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "30",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930166.4766111,
            "question": "Given the definition \"trenta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "November",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930299.211846,
            "question": "Given the definition \"novembre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "40",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930217.775202,
            "question": "Given the definition \"quaranta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "October",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930242.5368457,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ottobre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "50",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930517.573333,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cinquanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Thursday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930397.14652,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Giovedi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "trenta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444929979.7470803,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"30\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "9",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930046.3380983,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nove\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "tredici",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930460.2587316,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"13\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "otto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930131.1131485,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"8\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "1",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930128.625244,
            "question": "Given the definition \"uno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "aprile",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930080.7424593,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"April\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "dieci",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930095.4607854,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"10\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "12",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930519.9757373,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dodici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "16",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930157.7829957,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sedici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "settembre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930350.7463377,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"September\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "70",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930208.5118854,
            "question": "Given the definition \"settanta\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "5",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930205.23588,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cinque\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "13",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930313.5576718,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tredici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "11",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930260.0831769,
            "question": "Given the definition \"undici\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "September",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930017.817448,
            "question": "Given the definition \"settembre\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "100",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930090.4300764,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cento\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Monday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930303.720254,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lenedi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sunday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930178.3950322,
            "question": "Given the definition \"domencia\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "venti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930440.3012965,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"20\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "2",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930366.7363658,
            "question": "Given the definition \"due\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "19",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1444930077.762854,
            "question": "Given the definition \"diciannove\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}